<resources>
    <string name="app_name">StartPage</string>

    <string name="aboutRSAMI">In 1949, the need for a Central Sports and Games ground for Southern command was felt and General Maharaja Shri Rajendra Sinhji, D.S.O, GOC-in-C Southern Command, ordered the Polo Club ground to be leveled to accommodate a Cricket, Football and  Hockey ground……………..

….approached Poona club…… The Poona club, however, could not find their way to meet this request……….

……..It was then decided by the GOC-in-C to start in a small way………………..An open air dance was organized on 15th March 1950 to collect funds and at the same time mark the opening of the institute………….

………..A meeting of the officers of the Poona Garrison was held and the officers unanimously requested General Rajendra Sinhji to agree to the club being called ‘The Rajendra Sinhji Army Mess and Institute for Defense Services Officers’

Thus on 20th April 1950 the Rajendra Sinhji Army Mess and Institute officially came into being ……………
………….The motto approved for the Institute is ‘Comradeship through Sport’……………..</string>

    <string name="affiliations">1.	DSOI Bhopal \n

2.	DSOI Jhansi\n

3.	Officers Institute, Jodhpur\n

4.	Golden Katar Officers Institute, Ahmedabad\n

5.	Chinkara Officer Institute, Jaipur\n

6.	Officer Institute, Nasirabad\n

7.	Sarvatra Officers, Institute\n

8.	Army Officers Institute, Jamnagar\n

9.	DSOI, Udaipur\n

10.	AOI, Juhu and AOI Colaba (Extn of AOI Juhu)\n

11.	Temple Hill Institute, Deolali\n

12.	Sarath Institute, Ahmednagar\n

13.	Kamptee Club, Kamptee\n

14.	YSG ( Yuvraj Fatehsinh Rao Gymkhana ) Club Baroda\n

15.	DSOI, Kolhapur\n

16.	Parbat Ali Officers  Institute, Gandhinagar\n

17.	RSI Bangalore\n

18.	RSI Secunderabad\n

19.	DOI Cannanore\n

20.	Pangode Club at Trivendrum\n

21.	Meads Club, Belgaum\n

22.	U S Club, Mumbai\n

23.	Shahbaar officers Institute, Lucknow\n

24.	Officers  Institute, Gwalior\n

25.	DSOI, Dhaula Kaun , New Delhi\n

26.	DSOI, Chandigarh\n

27.	DSOI, Gurgaon</string>

    <string name="membershipRules">
        RULES OF CONDUCT FOR MEMBERS,DEPENDENTS
AND GUESTS (ISSUED IN APRIL 2010)

STATUS OF RSAMI, PUNE

HEADQUARTERS SOUTHERN COMMAND,PUNE- 411 001. GOC-IN-C SOUTHERN COMMAND IS THE CHIEF PATRON
OF RSAMI, PUNE.

YEARLY SUBSCRIPTION

PLATES, STRAWS AND POSTAL CHARGES ) FOR THE PERIOD FROM 26 MAR 2011 TO 25 MAR 2012 HAVE BEEN
CHARGED TO ALL THE MEMBERS IN THE BILL FOR THE MONTH OF FEB 11.

2
THE AMOUNT IS REQUIRED TO BE PAID BY 25 MAR EVERY YEAR. PAYMENT OF SUBSCRIPTION, IF NOT
RECEIVED BY 25 MAR 11, WILL ATTRACT AN INTEREST OF 1% ON THE BILL. IF THE BILL IS NOT CLEARED
TILL 25 APR 2011, ACTION WILL BE TAKEN TO TERMINATE THE MEMBERSHIP.

ENTRY INTO RSAMI

3. POSSESSION OF RSAMI, PUNE MEMBERSHIP/DEPENDENT CARD IS MANDATORY FOR ENTRY INTO RSAMI. NO ENTRY
SHALL BE PERMITTED WITHOUT MEMBERSHIP/DEPENDENT CARDS. DEPENDENTS UNDER NON- ENTITLED
CATEGORY WILL NOT BE PERMITTED WITHOUT THE MEMBER ACCOMPANYING THEM INTO RSAMI PUNE.

4. MEMBERS/DEPENDENTS ARE REQUESTED TO SHOW THEIR MEMBERSHIP/DEPENDENT CARDS WHEN ASKED BY
THE STAFF ON DUTY/ VENDORS / BAR, TRINCO, CAFÉ CODE RED AND SAI CHAT COUNTER. THE MEMBERSHIP
CARD IS A PROPERTY OF RSAMI, PUNE. ANY MISUSE/ FRAUDELENT USE WILL BE AN OFFENCE UNDER IPC.

PAYMENTS OF BILLINGS

5. (a) IT HAS BEEN OBSERVED WITH CONCERN THAT SOME MEMBERS DO NOT PAY THEIR RSAMI BILLS IN FULL. AS
PER PARAGRAPH 82 OF RSAMI RULES AND BYE LAWS-2006,PART I,PART PAYMENT OF BILL IS NOT ACCEPTABLE.
THIS RULE HAS BEEN REITERATED IN PARAGRAPH 6 OF RULES OF CONDUCT FOR MEMBERS,DEPENDENTS AND
GUESTS (APR 2009).

 (b) IN CASE THE BILL IS PAID IN PART, IT WILL BE EQUATED WITH NON PAYMENT OF BILL FOR WHICH THE CREDIT
FACILITY WILL BE STOPPED AFTER TWO CONSECUTIVE MONTHS FROM THE DATE OF ISSUE OF BILL. THE SAME
MAY LEAD TO TERMINATION OF MEMBERSHIP WITHOUT NOTICE AFTER TWO MONTHS. (PARAGRAPHS 50 (e), 53,
82 TO 84 OF RSAMI RULES AND BYE LAWS - 2006 REFER).

REFUND OF WRONG BILLING

6. MEMBERS ARE REQUESTED TO PAY THE RSAMI BILL FIRST AND THEN RAISE OBSERVATIONS, IF ANY. RSAMI WILL
NOT BE RESPONSIBLE FOR REFUND IN CASE CREDIT CHITS ARE NOT RECEIVED BY THE SECRETARY/RSAMI WITHIN
ONE MONTH.

PENALTY FOR BOUNCING OF CHEQUES

7. PENALTY OF Rs 200/- WILL BE IMPOSED ON DEFAULTING MEMBERS IF THE CHEQUES ARE BOUNCED OR
RETURNED DUE TO FAULTY WRITING OF CHEQUES, LACK OF SIGNATURES, DATE,ON FIRST OFFENCE.
HOWEVER, IF THE OFFENCE IS REPEATED MORE THAN TWICE IN A YEAR, MEMBERSHIP MAY BE TERMINATED.

ELIGIBILITY OF DEPENDENT MEMBERS

8. DEPENDENTS OF MEMBERS ARE PERMITTED TO USE RSAMI FACILITIES AS UNDER :-
 	(a) SONS. TILL THEY GET EMPLOYED OR ATTAIN THE AGE OF 25 YEARS, WHICHEVER IS EARLIER.
 	(b) DAUGHTERS. TILL THEY GET EMPLOYED OR MARRIED, WHICHEVER IS EARLIER.
 	(c) DEPENDENT PARENTS ( PART II ORDER COPY MUST BE PRODUCED).
 	(d) AFTER ATTAINING THE AGE OF 22 YEARS, THE MEMBER MUST PRODUCE THE PROOF OF DEPENDENTS
 	THAT THEY ARE STILL IN COLLEGE. THE MEMBERSHIP CARDS AFTER 22 YEARS OF AGE WILL BE RENEWED
 	ONLY FOR THREE MONTHS.

9. MEMBERS ARE REQUESTED TO CHANGE THE STATUS OF THEIR CHILDREN ON OCCURRENCE AND SURRENDER
THEIR DEPENDENT CARDS IMMEDIATELY THEREAFTER.

GUEST ENTRY

10. DETAILS OF GUESTS WILL BE REGISTERED IN GUEST REGISTER AT RECEPTION PRIOR TO THEIR ENTRYINTO
RSAMI. THE DEFAULTING MEMBERS WILL BE LIABLE FOR PENALTY CHARGES AT THE DISCRETION OF THE
MANAGEMENT.

11. SERVING OFFRS, NON MEMBER AND MEMBERS OF AFFILIATED INSTITUTES, ARE PERMITTED TO
BRINGGUESTS ONLY AFTER TAKING PERMISSION FROM SECRETARY, RSAMI, PUNE.

12. WHILE BUYING GUEST COUPONS, MEMBERS ARE REQUESTED TO DECLARE THE CATEGORY OF
THEIRGUESTS AS ABOVE AND PROVE THEIR IDENTITY BY SHOWING RSAMI/DEF IDENTITY CARDS OF SERVING
/RETDOFFRS AND RSAMI DEPENDENTS CARDS. MEMBERS ARE REQUESTED TO ENSURE THAT THEIR GUESTS
AREPROPERLY DRESSED AS PER THE DRESS CODE. OR ELSE, THE ENTRY IN RSAMI WILL NOT BE PERMITTED.


13. ONLY THE FOLLOWING CATEGORIES OF GUESTS ARE PERMITTED ON SATURDAYS ON PROVING THEIR

IDENTITIES :-

(a) SONS, DAUGHTERS, SONS-IN-LAW, DAUGHTERS-IN-LAWS, GRAND CHILDREN AND PARENTS.

(b) SERVING AND RETD OUT STATION DEFENCE OFFICERS WHO ARE NOT MEMBERS OF RSAMI,PUNE AND ARE ON
VISIT TO PUNE WITH PERMISSION OF MANAGER RSAMI,PUNE. SUCH OFFICERS ARE NOT ENTITLED TO BRING ANY
GUESTS.

(c) SERVING OFFICERS IN STATION WHO ARE NOT MEMBERS OF RSAMI, PUNE WITH THE PERMISSION OF MANAGER
(ON PRODUCTION OF IDENTITY CARD ONLY).

14. NOT MORE THAN SIX GUESTS ARE PERMITTED AT A TIME. NO PARTICULAR GUEST IS TO BE INTRODUCEDIN
THE RSAMI BY ONE MEMBER MORE THAN FOUR TIMES IN A MONTH. TO BRING MORE GUESTS, PRIOR PERMISSION
FROM MANAGER, RSAMI IS REQUIRED TO BE TAKEN.

15. A RSAMI MEMBER WHOSE MEMBERSHIP HAS BEEN TERMINATED FOR ANY REASON CANNOT BE INTRODUCED AS
A GUEST AT RSAMI BY ANY OTHER MEMBER.

RSAMI DRESS CODE

16. AS PER PARA 126 OF RSAMI RULES AND BYE LAWS-06, PART-I, RSAMI DRESS CODE IS AS UNDER :-
 	(a) GENTLEMEN (INCLUDING BOYS ABOVE 12 YEARS OF AGE).
 	(i) LOUNGE SUIT/COMBINATION/NATIONAL DRESS WITH LEATHER SHOES WITH SOCKS ; OR,
 	(ii) FULL SLEEVES SHIRT WITH NECK TIE, TROUSERS,LEATHER SHOES WITH SOCKS ; OR,
 	(iii) FULL/HALF SLEEVES SHIRT (TUCKED IN) WITH OPEN COLLARS/POLO SHIRTS (WITH COLLARS), TROUSERS
 	,/ JEANS AND LEATHER SHOES WITH SOCKS ; OR
 	(iv) SAFARI SUIT AND LEATHER SHOES WITH SOCKS.
 	(v) SIKH GENTLEMEN (INCLUDING BOYS ABOVE 18 YEARS OF AGE) MUST WEAR TURBANS.

ITEMS OF DRESS NOT PERMITTED TO BE WORN BY GENTLEMEN.

 	(i) COLLARLESS SHIRTS,TEE-SHIRTS (WITHOUTCOLLARS),SHORTS, SHORT SHIRTS,UNTUCKED SHIRTS,
 	DHOTI KURTA,PAIJAMA, TRADITIONAL DRESSES,SPORTS SHOES AND SANDALS.
 	(ii) SIKH GENTLEMEN ARE NOT PERMITTED TO WEAR PATKAS AND CAPS.
 	(iii) WEARING OF JEANS OF ANY TREND( FADED and RIPPED / TORN) BY THE MEMBERS, THEIR DEPENDENTS AND
 	GUESTS IS NOT PERMITTED.
 	(c) LADIES (INCLUDING YOUNG LADIES). THEY ARE REQUESTED TO BE APPROPRIATELY DRESSED AS PER
 	NORMS AND TRADITIONS OF OUR SOCIETY AND CULTURE.
 	(d) RSAMI DRESS CODE IS APPLICABLE ON ENTERING THE MAIN GATE OF RSAMI, PUNE.


RSAMI CODE OF CONDUCT

17. THE FOLLOWING WILL BE CONSIDERED AS VIOLATION OF RSAMI CO DE OF CONDUCT :-
(a) NOT BRINGING RSAMI MEMBERSHIP/ DEPENDENT CARDS	- A FINE OF Rs 200/- PER MEMBER.
(b) NOT MAKING/MAKING WRONG ENTRY OF GUEST IN THEGUEST BOOK	- A FINE OF Rs 200/- PER DEFAULT.
(c) VIOLATION OF RSAMI DRESS CODE	- A FINE OF Rs 200/- PER DEFAULT.
(d) MISBEHAVIOUR OR UN-GENTLEMANLY/ UNBECOMINGCONDUCT	- TERMINATION OF MEMBERSHIP.

MOVIE ENTRY COUPONS:

18. MEMBERS CAN BOOK MOVIE ENTRY COUPONS FOUR DAYS IN ADVANCE FOR THE MOVIES SCHEDULED FOR
THE FORTHCOMING BETWEEN 0900-1400 H. MEMBERS, DEPENDENTS AND THEIR REPRESENTATIVES ARE
REQUIRED TO PRODUCE THEIR MEMBERSHIP CARDS FOR OBTAINING MOVIE ENTRY COUPONS, OR ELSE, THEY
WILL BE CHARGED @ RS 90/- PER MOVIE ENTRY COUPONS. MOVIE ENTRY COUPONS ARE NON -TRANSFERABLE.
NO CANCELLATION OF MOVIE ENTRY COUPONS IS PERMITTED.

BUSINESS ACTIVITY / MEETING

19. PLEASE DO NOT USE RSAMI PREMISES FOR CARRYING OUT ‘BUSINESS MEETINGS’. OR ELSE, ACTION MAY BE
TAKEN TO TERMINATE THE MEMBERSHIP.

VISITING OFFICES AT RSAMI

20. MEMBERS ARE REQUESTED NOT TO VISIT RSAMI OFFICES BETWEEN 27 TO 30/31OF THE MONTH, AS RSAMI OFFICE
STAFF REMAINS ENGAGED IN PREPARATION AND DESPATCH OF MONTHLY BILLS. MEMBERS MAY VISIT THE
SECRETARY BETWEEN 1100H TO 1300H ONLY. CO-OPERATION OF THE MEMBERS IS SOLICITED PLEASE.

PARKING OF CARS IN RSAMI, PUNE

21. MEMBERS ARE REQUESTED TO PARK THEIR CARS IN EARMARKED AREAS INSIDE AND OUTSIDE RSAMI IN A
MANNER THAT THEIR CARS DO NOT OBSTRUCT THE WAY OF OTHER CARS. CAR PARKING INSIDE RSAMI COMPLEX IS
ONLY WITH CAR STICKERS ISSUED BY THE RSAMI MANAGEMENT TO AUTHORISED MEMBERS. WRONGLY PARKED
CARS MAY BE TOWED AWAY BY CIVIL TRAFFIC POLICE AT THE RISK AND COST OF DEFAULTING RSAMI MEMBER.
AUTHORISATION OF CAR PARKING STICKERS IS AS UNDER :-

 	(a) MAJ GEN and ABOVE and SENIOR CITIZEN ABOVE 75 YEARS OF AGE. INSIDE CAR (ORANGE HALF MOON).
 	(b) ALL OTHER MEMBERS. OUTSIDE CAR PARK (WHITE COLOUR).
 	(c) THE CARS OF MEMBERS WITH WHITE COLOUR STICKERS MAY BE PARKED IN THE ‘INSIDE CAR PARK’ IN
 	TILED PORTION, ON FIRST COME FIRST SERVE BASIS ONLY.
 	(d) TARMAC PORTION OF ‘ INSIDE CAR PARK’ IS RESERVED FOR MAJ GEN AND ABOVE AND MEMBERS ABOVE
 	75 YEARS OF AGE ISSUED WITH ORANGE COLOUR STICKER.
 	(e) ON SPECIAL OCCASSIONS, MAJOR/MINOR FUNCTION SPECIAL INSTRUCTION FOR CAR PARKING WILL BE
 	APPLICABLE.

RIGHT TO ADMISSION
22. IGNORANCE OF ABOVE RULES OF CONDUCT FOR MEMBERS, DEPENDENTS AND GUESTS IS NO EXCUSE AND
SHALL NOT BE ACCEPTED BY MANAGEMENT RSAMI, PUNE. BY APPLYING FOR RSAMI,PUNE MEMBERSHIP, THE MEMBERS
AUTOMATICALLY UNDERTAKE TO ABIDE BY THE RSAMI RULES AND BYE LAWS AND INSTRUCTIONS ISSUED FROM
TIME TO TIME THROUGH RSAMI NEWS LETTERS/NOTICE BOARD/CINEMA SLIDES.

23. RIGHT OF ADMISSION RESERVED AND GOVERNED BY RSAMI, PUNE RULES AND BYE LAWS AND INSTRUCTIONS
ISSUED FROM TIME TO TIME.

PAYMENT OF RSAMI BILLS

24. IN CASE RSAMI, PUNE BILL FOR A MONTH IS NOT RECEIVED BY 10TH OF THE NEXT MONTH DUE TO POSTAL
DELAY / NON DELIVERY OF BILLS BY POSTMAN, PLEASE MAKE ENQUIRIES FROM RECEPTIONIST ON TELE NO.
020-26102917 / 26361105 OR BY PERSONAL VISIT. IT MAY KINDLY BE NOTED THAT IT IS THE RESPONSIBILITY OF
THE MEMBERS ALSO TO ASCERTAIN OUTSTANDING BILLS AND MAKE PAYMENTS IN TIME TO AVOID ANY .
EMBARRASMENT OR INCONVENIANCE

25. IF THE BILLS ARE NOT PAID WITHIN 30 DAYS, i.e, BY 24TH OF THE NEXT MONTH 2% INTEREST WILL BELEVIED
BY THE COMPUTERISED BILLING SYSTEM AND THE SAME CAN NOT BE CONDONED.
    </string>

	<string name="contactUs">RAJENDRA SINHJI ARMY MESS AND INSTITUTE, \n Pune
(A COMBINED OFFICERS\' MESS)

No 1, Ashoka Marg, Pune- 411001\n
Maharashtra, INDIA

Tel : (020) 26022917, 26361105\n

Email: rsipune@gmail.com\n

Website: www.rsipune.org</string>

	<string name="theatreInfo">400 seater Open Air Theatre with outdoor snack counters is for screening training/other Films and plays / drama.</string>

	<string name="eventLawnInfo">A sprawling expanse of well manicured greens allow for hosting Outdoor Events, Official Functions and Gatherings. The lawns really come into its own on Special Days.</string>

	<string name="hallInfo">Over 500 people can be accommodated in this large Hall available for Training, Official Functions,official seminars and Multi Functions.</string>

	<string name="guestRoomInfo">Five well furnished air-conditioned rooms are available on a first-come basis to offices on official visit. For allotment please Contact Asst Secyin RSI office.</string>

	<string name="barInfo">Well stocked Bars on two floors are air conditioned for the use by the members only.</string>

	<string name="trincoInfo">Multi-Cuisine are served during the Lunch and Dinner timings with buffet facilities on Saturdays and Sundays. Party rooms provides fine dining experience to the members.</string>

	<string name="cafeInfo">A coffee shop with steaming hot cups of Tea and coffee complemented with an array of bakery and fast food items are available to the members..</string>

	<string name="billiardInfo">At RSAMI you will find high quality Billiards table which enables members to practice concerntration and aming.</string>

</resources>
